Hello, this is Sayu Kanagawa.
Yes, as you can see from the view, I'm here to ski.
I came here to ski!
I'm so happy!
This is the second time, the second time!
I never thought I would be able to ski again so soon.
I'm very excited.
It's getting a little bit warmer and the snow is changing a lot.
I think the snow condition is changing a lot now that it's getting warmer.
I'm looking forward to seeing how the snow is changing.
I'm looking forward to enjoying this second installment of the tour.
So, the place we are visiting today is
Octone Snow Park!
Here we are today!
Today's video will be a video of me just skiing and just having fun.
I hope you will enjoy it!
Okay, I'm off.
Thank you very much for watching!
OK, here it comes!
OK! That was fast!
That was a little scary!
I'm not gonna lie, it was a little scary!
Did you see my last ski video? Did you guys see the last ski video?
They said I was pretty good...
I was so happy to hear that.
And I did surprisingly well for that.
It's like...
If I can do it better, I can become a pro.
Ha-ha-ha.
How far are you going? I thought.
I was so happy!
Looking forward to your commercial!
Your Service
agenic
WIN!
I laughed so hard... at how good your father was at it.
I was so happy because, as I told you last time, he trained me for the first time in a very sudden situation, and I told him that I was so good and that he was so good.
I told him that I wanted to go with him when I went back to Hokkaido, but I couldn't compete with him because of his work.
I told my dad that I wanted to go skiing with him when I came back to Hokkaido, but his work was too much to compete with.
I'd like to go skiing and visit the ski resorts in Hokkaido someday.
I'd love to go skiing in Hokkaido someday, and I'd also like to go out for dinner, which would be great because I can take pictures of that too.
I'll have to make an appeal!
Arrival
It's so beautiful!
Amazing!
I think she's a little surprised.
Oh, my God, they changed the camera.
It's a much better camera.
That's great.
Well, I'm looking forward to another great day of skiing.
I'm off!
Go!
Wow! So soft!
Feels good! It's so soft!
Oh, man!
Yuck!
There you go!
No! Wait! I'm scared!
I'm a little scared! Today!
Mmm-hmm.
Ha!
Yoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
It's so beautiful! The view is amazing!
Oh, no.
I'm better at this.
Yoo-hoo!
Stop!
Okay, okay.
Oh, man.
I'm feeling a little blank.
How long has it been?
Two months? I haven't skied at all.
I don't know what to do.
But it's so beautiful, isn't it?
I was just admiring the view.
Yes, sir.
Oh, no! I'm riding the lift alone!
It's beautiful!
Look at that snow mountain!
That snow mountain over there.
This is the first place I thought I'd go.
Because there's so much snow!
I see. YouTubers are like this.
I might be a little embarrassed to talk.
I don't get a lot of snow when I'm wearing skis.
I just thought about that.
It was fine last time, and it's fine today, too!
Yay!
This snow might be hard to ski!
I've skied it twice.
I can't get used to it.
I don't know...
I think my legs might have lost a lot of weight.
You know...
I wonder if "Twice Upon a Dream" is on sale...
Is it on sale now?
I am.
I'm participating in it as a unit.
Never Say Never
There is a song called "Never Say Never" in which I participate as a unit.
It's a really good song.
It's amazing!
I'm so happy to be a member who likes baseball
I'm so happy to be a part of this group
I'm so happy
But I still haven't done the fox dance
I'm still trying to learn about baseball
I have not had a chance to learn more about baseball
I had a chance to learn more about baseball
I've been trying to learn more about baseball
I guess you could say I'm a bit of a mehaholic
I guess you could say
I'm at a level where everyone else is at 100
but I haven't even reached the level of 1 yet.
so I have to learn more and more.
I have to learn more and more.
First of all, I was very happy to be able to work on this project.
the music.
I think it's my favorite song
I think it's going to be my favorite song in Nogizaka.
This song
And
I think most people will cry
when they hear this song.
Because even the members were already crying
Yuna too
Kuromi
When I heard it
I said, "This makes me cry.
We were all talking about it.
It was a really great song.
I cried.
So, we are now at the intermediate course.
It still looks okay, but I'm afraid of not being able to see what's ahead, but I'm going to keep going and do my best.
Look over here, there are so many trees!
Oh my God, can you see the airplane cloud? Where?
Where? Can't you see it? It's just a thin layer.
Just find it, please.
There's an airplane cloud. I'm going to slide down.
Okay, here we go.
Ha!
Oh, this snow is so good!
I love this snow.
Yay!
It's so nice.
You can ski while looking at the view.
Whoo!
Yoo-hoo!
Hey!Hey!
It's super pretty, the view.
Wow!
Wai wai wai wai wai wai!
Wow, maybe a little intermediate!
Intermediate! Oh, no!
Intermediate!
It's too intermediate! Oh, my God.
Oh no!
It's too intermediate!
No! No!
Oh no!
You made me feel good about leaving.
It's definitely going to grow back.
No, seriously.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I didn't know grade 10 was so awesome!
Oh no!
I'm so horny!
Watch out!
Too intermediate
It's too intermediate!
It was scary, wasn't it?
It was so scary.
That's good. That's good.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm getting used to the top.
It's great, but it's not as bad as I thought.
Intermediate.
You made it.
Just in time.
There's some kind of stick.
Is that it?
Is that the stick?
Maybe...
I want to do it.
I want to try it for the first time.
What's the name of this? What's the name?
Pole Barn.
Pole Burn
Pole Barn
First try Pole Barn
40 seconds to start with
I want to go first!
Let's go for it!
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Oh, I'm scared.
On the right.
Fast forward.
Oh, no.
Oh, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Hi!!!!
Aww!
What? 50 seconds?
Whoa!
I totally thought I got 30 seconds.
58 seconds!
No, wait, I'm sorry.
No, I can do it. I can do it.
But it was a little steep at the beginning.
Once you get over that...
You've already done the rest on the inside.
If you work hard at the beginning, you can do it.
Oh, I want to go! I want to go again!
Let's go!
Wow, I'm so frustrated!
58 seconds.
I tried it anyway, but it was super fun!
It was a lot of fun.
I don't know, but the first part was a little scary, but once I got over that part, the rest was just...
I had so much fun, so much fun. I managed to get through the first part and it was 58 seconds.
I was so surprised. 58 seconds... I thought it was a joke, but...
I'm going to try to do 40 seconds this time.
All right, second time, then.
Oh, my God.
40 seconds!
I'm going for 40 seconds! I'm going for it!
The first time I'm not afraid.
Okay!
I'm going for it! Here I go!
Here we go!
Let's go!
Let's go! Go for it!
[ED]
It's early! Absolutely fast!
Absolutely fast! This one!
Wow!
41 seconds!
I'm so happy! Oh my gosh!
That was so good!
That was amazing! I'm so happy!
Wow! We made it!
What?
40 seconds is my goal. Well, sure, but I'm in first place!
But I'm so happy! 41 seconds! I can do it!
I'm going pro! This is so much fun!
Now that we've skated a bit, let's go to dinner! Lunch! Lunch!
I've been looking forward to lunch!
I'm running out of energy!
I think I'll have curry.
So many curries!
I'll definitely have curry!
Well, the curry has arrived!
There you go!
My hands are shaking, but I hope it's okay.
I can't use it.
It looks so delicious!
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
Mmm!
Mmmm!
No, it's more curry than I like, that's for sure.
Mmm!
Bon appétit.
Mmm! Delicious!
So, I finished eating my rice.
It was so delicious. Thank you for the meal.
Now I am going to try snowboarding again, which I tried for the first time last time.
Last time I couldn't ski very well,
The first time I tried snowboarding, it was so bad that I had to hold on to my buttocks to keep going,
After that, I was able to ski in a straight line,
This time, I had watched the video and studied it beforehand,
I've watched the video and I've done some preparation, so I'm going to show it to the best of my ability this time.
I've watched the video and I've done my prep work, so I'm going to give it my best shot.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, if you push, soft, evenly soft, good!
Wow! I can do it!
Yes, yes, yes, feel the snow scraping off your heel, whew! Yum!
Isn't it good?
One hit!
That's great!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Oh!
Wait, isn't that good? It's so good, isn't it?
Left hand, left foot.
Okay, no fear, no fear.
We're going to turn the board vertical.
Turn the board up, back, back, back.
That's good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
here you go.
Left foot, left hand.
Brake, brake, brake, brake.
No fear, no fear. I'm going to turn the board over.
Swing back, heel up. Tip.
Good, good. Don't turn around, don't turn around.
I've got it, I've got it, I've got it, I've got it, I've got it.
Ouch.
Left hand, left foot.
Oh, I thought not.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I've built up a lot of courage.
Oh, you're sleeping.
Yes, flatten. Yes, new in heel.
Yes, left hand extended.
New on your toes.
Yes, look back the other way.
Aah!
Yes!
Yeah!
I did it!
We did it!
You did it! You did it!
That was good!
That was great!
Oh, man! I did it!
I could ski!
So, that's the end of the ski snubber!
Yes, it was a lot of fun. The weather was a lot warmer than the last time we skied,
So I was a little scared of the snow, but I had a lot of fun skiing the intermediate course,
I skied the intermediate course, which was surprisingly difficult, but I had a lot of fun. I didn't think I could snub board this much anymore, so I was really happy,
I would definitely like to go snaboing again so that I can ski more in a row in the shape of leaves.
So, thank you for watching today. Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button. Bye bye!